privatepornos.com 2018-08-15

# Privacy Policy - Vod-Club

At vod-club.videobox.com, we understand that sharing your personal information with us over the Internet requires trust. We value your trust very highly, and Vod-Club believes in protecting the privacy of our subscribers, audiences, and other visitors to the vod-club.videobox.com website (our " **Site** "). This Privacy Policy describes our privacy practices on our Site and all related online and mobile applications and services that we provide (our " **Services** "). The following information is designed to help you understand how we collect, use, disseminate and safeguard the information you provide to us while accessing and using our Site and Services.

Your use of our Site or Services indicates your acceptance of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with our information practices, please do not access or use our Site or Services. As provided below, we reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, add or remove portions of this policy at any time by posting such changes to this page. Such changes will be effective upon posting.

Our Site is designed to stream and otherwise distribute content and provide fun interaction to you for your entertainment purposes. Our Services available through our Site include watching, creating clips of, commenting on, and sharing content as well as interacting with others via the Internet including but not limited to playing games, chatting, and other Internet-based methods of interaction.

### Types of Information We Collect

In order to better serve you, we gather two types of information from you when you visit our Site or use our Services: (1) anonymous usage or statistical information that does not, by itself, identify you, such as, for example, what browser or device you are using to access our Site or Services, and your Internet Protocol (IP) address; and (2) personally identifiable information, which is information that lets us know the specifics of who you are, such as, for example, your first and last name, mailing address, email address, telephone number, credit card information, purchase history, and your username and password for our Site.

### How We Collect Information

**Anonymous Information and Cookies**

When you visit our Site, you will be assigned a permanent "cookie" (a small, unique identifier text file) to be stored on your computer's hard drive. The purpose of the cookie is to identify you when you visit our Site so we can enhance and customize your online experience. You can choose to use our Site or Services without cookies if you wish. To use our Site without cookies, you can configure your browser to reject all cookies or notify you when a cookie is set. (Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences.) If you reject cookies from our Site, some parts of our Site or Services may not work properly. The cookies on our Site and in our Services may come from us, from third party ad serving companies that display banner or other advertisements, or from our partners who help provide our Site and Services to you.

We may also collect other information from you when you use our Site or Services, including IP addresses, information about which browser, operating system, and device you used to access our Site or Services, how you found our Site or Services (e.g., the previously visited page or search terms), date and time of your visit, your browsing habits or preferences in using our Site and Services, the state or country from which you accessed our Site or Services, or the number of pages you visited or links you clicked on within our Site.

We collect this anonymous information on both an individual and aggregate basis. However, Vod-Club does not associate this anonymous information with your personally identifiable information.

**Personally Identifiable Information**

Unless you log into our Site, subscribe for our Services, or otherwise voluntarily provide personally identifiable information to us, your visit to our Site or use of our Services is anonymous. Vod-Club does not collect any personally identifiable information about you except when you voluntarily provide it to us, such as when you subscribe to our Site, use our Services, sign up for email news, fill out a form, or send us feedback. When you are logged into your account, your browsing activities are logged into a secure database that helps us create personalized recommendations for you. You may also provide personally identifiable information to us indirectly through third parties with whom we have an arrangement that permits us to integrate their service offerings with our own.

You may visit our Site without subscribing, and you are free to choose whether or not to provide any personally identifiable information to us. However, you will not be able to view our entire Site nor use all of our Services if you do not subscribe and provide the requested information.

### How We Use the Information We Collect

Vod-Club uses your anonymous and personally identifiable information to provide and enhance our Site and our Services to you, including but not limited to the fulfillment of your requests, the creation and delivery of your transaction records, and the communication to you of information about our Site, our Services, or your subscription. We may also use your anonymous and personally identifiable information to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, assess our demographic reach, statistically analyze use of our Site and Services or our advertising responses, and to customize the content, layout, and features of our Site and Services. Our Site contains personalization features that collect data from your browsing, viewing and searching activities to provide custom movie and scene recommendations for you and to otherwise personalize your Site experience. Vod-Club may aggregate this type of otherwise personally identifiable information into anonymous or statistical data to study overall usage trends and to make improvements to our Site's usability.

Of course, we also may use your personally identifiable information to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems with our Site, Services, or systems, and enforce our agreements with you, including but not limited to this Privacy Policy.

### How We Share Your Information

**Anonymous Information**

We may share aggregated demographic and statistical information with our partners, sponsors, advertisers, vendors and other third parties. Such aggregated information is not linked to any personally identifiable information that can identify any individual person.

**Personally Identifiable Information**

Except as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy, Vod-Club will not share your personally identifiable information with any third party without your permission.

If you choose to use any of our Services delivered in conjunction with any of our partners, including but not limited to channel upgrades and live cams, your information may be shared with such partners to the extent necessary to provide you with those Services and to accept payment from you for those Services.

You may receive emails sent by us, our direct partners, or by a company we contract with to send our emails. Vod-Club does not sell, trade, or rent any email addresses to other organizations or businesses.

Ordinarily, access to your personally identifiable information is restricted to Vod-Club employees. However, Vod-Club does contract with third party billing companies. The third party billing companies, which collect your payment for subscribing to our Site and using our Services, collect personal and billing information that we have access to but do not store. You acknowledge and agree that we do not have any responsibility for the collection, maintenance or safeguarding of the privacy of any such personal or billing information provided to such third party billing companies and that such responsibility is solely between you and the third party billing company. We encourage you to examine and determine your satisfaction with the policies of such third party billing companies prior to your using them. If you have questions regarding which third party billing companies we contract with, please contact us via our "Contact Us" page.

We may disclose personally identifiable information to third-party vendors or law enforcement officials in order to prevent abuse of, or harm to, our systems, Site, Services, subscribers, sponsors, users, or other members of our community. We may also cooperate with law enforcement agencies in providing personally identifiable information to identify anyone who may be using our Site or Services for illegal activities.

Additionally, Vod-Club may disclose your personally identifiable information as otherwise required by law, such as pursuant to a subpoena or other judicial or administrative order. If we are required by law to share information that you have submitted, we will attempt to provide you with notice (unless we are prohibited) that a request for your information has been made in order to give you an opportunity to object to the disclosure. Even if you object, we may be required to turn over your information.

Finally, we may provide any of your information to any parent, sister, or subsidiary organizations (in which case we will require such entities to honor this Privacy Policy) or to any organization we may acquire, by whom we may be acquired, or with whom we may merge.

### Information You Make Public

When you use our Site or Services, you may be given an opportunity to post comments or share your experiences with others in public areas. If you choose to include any personally identifiable or other information in a Site posting or other forum accessible to others, you do so at your own risk. For example, third parties may use such information to send you unsolicited messages. Vod-Club is not responsible for the disclosure or use of any information that you choose to post or otherwise make available to others through our Site or Services. If you do not want such information to be viewed by third parties, do not share it in public areas of our Site or Services.

### Security of Personally Identifiable Information

We attempt to protect your personally identifiable information from theft, loss, or alteration with security measures that are reasonable and consistent with industry standards. For example, we use encryption technologies whenever transferring certain types of sensitive information, such as credit card data.

Because you can access your personally identifiable information in your Vod-Club account through your username and password, it is important you not share your password with anyone. Always remember to log out of your account and close your browser window when you have finished your visit to our Site. This is to help ensure that others cannot access your account, especially if you are sharing a computer with someone else or are using a computer or mobile device in a public place, such as a library or cafÃ©. You are entirely responsible for any use or disclosure of your information by anyone to whom you have given your password.

### Links, Embedded Media, and Partners

Our Site contains links to other websites or services, as well as embedded graphics, videos, forms, or other media. These external sites and services have different privacy policies that Vod-Club does not control â please refer to each respective site for more information about the information each site collects and how each uses and shares that information. Vod-Club is not responsible for, and does not necessarily endorse, the content, products, or other materials accessible through third-party sites and services.

### No Children

You must be at least eighteen (18) years old to use our Site and Services. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from users under the age of eighteen.

### International Concerns

Because the Internet is global, information about you that we collect or that you submit to us may be transferred, processed, stored, and used in countries (including the United States) other than the one in which you live, where laws regarding processing of your personally identifiable information may be less stringent than the laws in your country. By using our Site or Services, you explicitly consent to such transfer, processing, storage, and use of your information.

### Opting-Out

You may remove yourself from our email lists at any point by clicking on the Unsubscribe link at the bottom of marketing and outreach emails that we send out. Alternately, you may log into your account and uncheck the email box to stop receiving emails, or email us via our "Contact Us" page if you would like to be removed from any of our email lists.

It may not be possible to opt out of all forms of information sharing and communication, unless you cancel your membership and all other transactions you have pending with Vod-Club. For example, we must provide certain data to credit card companies so that they can process transactions you request, and we will send order confirmations to you via e-mail whenever you make a purchase, regardless of your subscription status. Even if you terminate all ties to Vod-Club, we may maintain your information in our databases to the extent we are required to do so by law.

It may take us up to thirty (30) days to process any requests you make about your information, including any updates, requests to stop sharing your information, or removal requests. Vod-Club is not responsible for removing information about you from the databases of third parties to whom we were authorized to disclose your information prior to processing your removal request.

### Scope of This Privacy Policy

We may collect personally identifiable information about you in ways other than through our Site or Services, including via the phone, direct mail, in person, or through other communication channels. This Privacy Policy only governs the information we collect from you through our Site and Services. Our use and sharing of information we collect from you through other means is subject to applicable laws.

### How to Contact Us

If you have comments or questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us via our "Contact Us" page.

US Address:  
1625 Clay St. Ste. 300  
Oakland, CA 94612  
Phone: toll-free 877-387-9077

UK office (Please do not send correspondence):  
Unit 7, 15-17 Caledonian Road  
P.O. Box 268  
London England, N1 9DX

Meta Billing.com Incorporated:  
C18 the Sands, Bay Road. & George Street  
Basseterre, St-Kitts

### Changes to This Privacy Policy

We may change this Privacy Policy at any time. Such changes will be effective immediately upon our posting the revised Privacy Policy on our Site. Please review our Site and this Privacy Policy periodically so that you are aware of any modifications. Your continued use of the Site or Services after such modifications are made will constitute your acknowledgment of the modified Privacy Policy and your agreement to be bound by it.

_This policy was last updated on November 15, 2011._
